McCaddon Collection of the Barnum and Bailey Circus, 1871-1907 (bulk 1895-1905): Finding Aid TC040
Manuscripts Division
- Series 2: Scrapbooks, 1849-1968 December 19; 25 boxes
  - Scrapbook 21: Barnum & Bailey on Tour, 1903-1904 (photographs: only major photos are identified in this list), 1 box
    - Ticket wagon. R.F. (Tody) Hamilton. Clowning with mule. Two unidentified couples, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 37, Page 48)
  - Scrapbook 22: Wardrobe and Property Account, Fall of Babylon, Oakland Gardens, Boston, 1890; 1 box
    - description of property list, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 38, Page 17-23)
    - property list Victory Procession, Babylon, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 38, Page 25-30)
    - credit account, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 38, Page 40-41)
    - cash account, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 38, Page 43-44)
    - props packed, not in use, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 38, Page 51-58)
    - Babylon Armor list, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 38, Page 71)
    - Properties inventory, 1890, not in use, 1 box (Box 38, Page 83-84)
    - Properties inventory, 1890, in use, 1 box (Box 38, Page 85-87)
    - Wardrobe list, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 38, Page 92-99)
  - Scrapbook 23: European Tour, 1901; 1 box
    - Front pages of Couriers used in each town visited during the 1901 European tour. 1901 April 7 (Budapest, Hungary) - 1901 November 16 (Mons, Belgium), 1 box (Box 39)
    - Five different languages, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 39, Page 92-99)
    - Magyar - Hungarian, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 39, Page 1-2, Page 4-30)
    - German, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 39, Page 3, Page 31-37)
    - Bohemian, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 39, Page 38-39, Page 43-44)
    - Dutch - Holland, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 39, Page 95-112)
    - French - Belgium, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 39, Page 113-128)
  - Scrapbook 24: Barnum & Bailey, Information and Address Book, 1901-1903; 1 box
    - General Information and Address Book, business only. Includes lists of suppliers and business connections, children employed, Road Catering Privileges, Contracts, route mailing list, Measurements for poles, list of items in storage, Insurance Agreements, and Blacklists. All information is alphabetical, 1901-1903; 1 box (Box 40)
  - Scrapbook 25: Ringling Bros. and Barnum and Bailey Combined Shows, Season 1922, Coast to Coast, 1 box
    - Front Door, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 1)
    - Candystand, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 2)
    - Sideshow ticket stand, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 3)
    - View of sideshow and front door, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 4)
    - Sideshow at night, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 5)
    - Mr. Lew Graham, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 6)
    - Ticket sellers, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 7)
    - At the trains [?], dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 8)
    - Loading the train, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 9)
    - Doctor Shields, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 10)
    - Doctor Shields Hospital Tent, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 11)
    - Cook House, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 12)
    - Cook House Crew, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 13)
    - Putting up the big top, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 14)
    - Grant Park, Chicago, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 15)
    - Elephants, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 16)
    - Giraffes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 17)
    - Main Candy Stand, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 18)
    - Front Door Candy Stand, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 19)
    - Wallen, the man who puts it all up, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 20)
    - Sleeping Cars, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 21)
    - Ring Stock Rosin Backs, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 22)
    - Ring Stock Race Horses, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 23)
    - Miss Starks' Tigers, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 24)
    - Miss Starks' Tigers, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 25)
    - Equestrian Directors, Messrs. Bradna and Agee, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 26)
    - Front Door Staff, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 27)
    - Spec Costume, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 28)
    - Spec Flower Costumes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 29)
    - After a Fishing Trip, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 30)
    - Barber's Shop, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 31)
    - Menagerie, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 32)
    - Bears, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 33)
    - Ushers, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 34)
    - Interior of Big Top during the show, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 35)
    - Blacksmith's shop, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 36)
    - Interior of Blacksmith's shop, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 37)
    - Mr. Ringling's private tent, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 38)
    - Commissary, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 39)
    - Spessells Quick Lunch Auto, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 40)
    - Spessells Quick Lunch Auto, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 41)
    - Clarke Troupe, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 42)
    - Clarke Troupe, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 43)
    - Indians!, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 44)
    - Siegrist Troupe, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 45)
    - Performers carrying trunks, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 46)
    - Mrs. Car, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 47)
    - Albert Powell June, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 48)
    - Sie Takar Troupe [?], dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 49)
    - Huling's Pet Sea Lion, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 50)
    - Pad Room, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 51)
    - Siegrist Sisters, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 52)
    - Maynard the Cowboy, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 53)
    - Spec costumes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 54)
    - Spec costumes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 55)
    - Spec costume, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 56)
    - Spec costume, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 57)
    - Spec costume, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 58)
    - Spec costumes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 59)
    - Jim Spriggs, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 60)
    - Glen Graves Champion, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 61)
    - Merle Evans' Band, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 62)
    - Band in Spec Costume, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 63)
    - Clown Band, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 64)
    - Clowns, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 85, Page 65)
- Series 3: Miscellaneous Materials, 1683-1988 December 19; 44 boxes; 9 folders; 6 items
  Consists of deeds, contracts, correspondence, minute books, music, maps, handbills, artwork, and costume design, as well as other materials.
  Arranged by genre of material.
  This series contains harmful and offensive descriptions of people that may include racist, colonialist, ableist, and dehumanizing language. Some of the description is original to the donor and/or the creator, and in these instances of creator- and donor-supplied titles, description may be retained to convey contextual/historical information of the materials. Otherwise, descriptions derive from a typewritten inventory of the collection that may have been provided by the donor, or may have been created by an archivist.
  - Deeds, Contracts, Correspondence, 1876-1937; 1 box
    - Personal of both J.A. Bailey and J.T. McCaddon, 1884-1936, including personal memorandum book of Bailey, 1876-1877, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - 1890: Transactions re. McCaddon's move from Minn. Dime Shows to Forepaugh w/Cooper 1899 consolidation of B&B. 1894, misc, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - 1900: Transactions re. International exchange rate and Bailey's bank transfers. 1901 death and will related material of Dr. Stanton, veterinary surgeon for B&B, McCaddon executor. Misc, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - 1902: Money transfers, Bailey. 1903: Teamsters' demand of B&B, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - 1904: McCaddon's resignation as director of B&B. Bailey-McCaddon correspondence, purchase of Forepaugh-Sells. McCaddon-Bailey re. McCaddon's purchase of old B&B Paraphernalia Bailey-McCaddon and Bailey et. Al. re. McCaddon use of Hippodrome. 1905: death of Mayme McCaddon. Misc, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - 1906: Death of Bailey and complications, letters re. McCaddon's installation as Chairman of the Board. B&B correspondence re interest in Forepaugh-Sells Bros. Shows, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - 1907: Cody & Bailey - profit and loss account, correspondence. 1908 more Cody & Bailey. Unused certificate of incorporation of Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show. Correspondence re. law suits. J.T. McCaddon chairman and executor. 1909: B&B Ltd. liquidates, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - 1931: Re. cruelty to circus animals. J.T. McCaddon with Spectator, London. 1935: Seely-McCaddon re. "The Mighty Barnum." 1937: McCaddon, Major G.W. Lillie re. N.Y. World's Fair exhibit. Also letter to Kilpatrick re. use of Madison Square Garden Bowl for above exhibit, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Jumbo, Voyage across Atlantic, 1882; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 8)
      [missing 1982]
    - 1907: Contract between Barnum & Bailey Circus and Ringling Bros. 1908: Letter to J.T. McCaddon from Holmes & Rogers Lawyers. 1908: Letter to A.A. Stewart from Otto Ringling. 1908: Letter to A.A. Stewart from Charles Rogers. 1906: Minutes of Meeting of the Board of Directors of Barnum and Bailey, Ltd., 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - 1905-1906: Partnership Agreement-J.A. Bailey and Ringling Bros.; Sale of Estate of J.A. Bailey to Ringling Bros. Of the Adam Forepaugh and Sells Bros. Shows, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Contracts (Original Material and Photocopies), 1871-1908; 2 boxes; 2 items
    - Original Material, dates not examined; 1 item
    - 1871-1872. Agreement, J.E. Cooper with Bailey and Middleton, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Partnership agreement: J.E. Cooper, J.A. Bailey, Robert Hood, 1873; 1876; 1877; 1880; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Agreements: 1874: Lease on Louisville Exposition Building. 1877: Charter S.S. "Claudia Hamilton". 1878: Charter S.S. "Golden Sea", 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - 1876 & 1877: Cooper and Bailey in Australia, letters, programs, train agreements and schedules, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - 1883. Agreement: Hagan, Campbell & Young. T. Brandenburg 9th and Arch Museums, 1885 dissolution of above, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 1888-1895: Receipts, Barnum & Bailey Shows, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - 1890, 1891 Sale of Adam Forepaugh Shows to James E. Cooper. Partnership agreement. Barnum, Bailey & Cooper, Barnum Estate to Bailey & Cooper, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - 1891, Partnership agreement among J.A. Bailey, J.E. Cooper, J.T. McCaddon, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - 1892. Sale of Adam Forepaugh Shows from Estate of J.E. Cooper to J.A. Bailey and J.T. McCaddon, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - 1892 Partnership agreement: J.A. Bailey, J.T. McCaddon, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - 1897 - power of attorney for J.A. Bailey to J.T. McCaddon, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - 1893 Madison Square Garden Company. Bailey's allegations of mismanagement, communications, results, etc., 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - 1894-1902. Lease of Bridgeport Winter Quarters, Estate of P.T. Barnum to J.A. Bailey, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Smithsonian Institution, Zoological Park, Baker-Bailey correspondence re. exchange of lion, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - 1894. Purchase by J.A. Bailey from the Barnum Estate of half the interest in Barnum & Bailey. Agreement and various letters relating to it., 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Agreements 1895: Cody, Salsbury with J.A. Bailey 1897: Cody, Salsbury with J.A. Bailey 1902: Cody, Salsbury with B&B, Ltd., 1903: M.T. Cody with J.A. Bailey, 1904: Balance sheets of the Buffalo Bill Wild West Show, 1905: M.T. Cody with J.A. Bailey, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - 1895. Mayer-Bailey correspondence re. big elephant trade, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - 1897. English Winter Quarters, Agreement between J.A. Bailey and Mr. Renshaw, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - 1897 Agreement between J.A. Bailey and W.W. Cole, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - 1897. Partnership agreement between J.A. Bailey, Ruth L. Bailey, and J.T. McCaddon, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - 1899 to 1906. Agreement between Bailey & Cole and the Sells Bros, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Press comments - First company meeting of Barnum and Bailey, Ltd., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Formation of Stock Co. Sale by J.A. Bailey to B&B, Ltd. Agreement to defer dividends, grant American rights to title for five years, and the correspondence regarding it., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - 1902, 1905. Lease of Madison Square Garden, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - 1903-1906. Agreement: Barnum and Bailey with Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - 1903. Models of American War Vessels for Exhibition, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - 1905-1906. Partnership agreement: J.A. Bailey and Ringling Bros., Sale of Estate of J.A. Bailey to Ringling Bros. Sale of Adam Forepaugh and Sells Bros. Show, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - 1906. Agreement between Barnum and Bailey with Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - 1906-1908. Partnership Agreements: Estate of J.A. Bailey with W.F. Cody, 1907. Cody grants McCaddon power of attorney, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - 1907. Sale of Barnum and Bailey to Ringling Bros., B&B notices and memoranda, Haskins and Sells reports on B&B, 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Photocopies of Above Contracts, dates not examined; 29 folders (Box 43, Folder 1-29)
  - Minute Books, 1899 February 15-1905 April 3; 1 box
    - Barnum and Bailey Ltd., Minute Book no. 1 (no. 24). 1899 February 15 (first meeting) to 1905 March 24, 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Barnum and Bailey, Ltd., Minute Book no. 2 (no. 25). 1905 April 3 to April 26th, 1909 (final meeting), 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Documents, 1876-1904; 1 box
    - Mount Vernon Properties to J.A. Bailey from Dawson-Archer, Wright, Glover, Lyon. 1903-1904. Title Insurance deeds, 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Various building contracts for Mt. Vernon residence and grounds, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - 1901. Dr. Stanton's death certificate, 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - J.A. Bailey's proposal for "The New Circus" by J.T. McCaddon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Wills and Codicils of Phineas T. Barnum, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Barnum and Bailey report of directors, report to shareholders upon the occasion of J.A. Bailey's death, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Memorandum and articles of association, B&B, first proof and final copy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Cash book, Cooper and Bailey, Australia and South American tours, 1876; 1877; 1878; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Bailey and McCaddon Estates. Misc. lists of possessions, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Route Books, 1863-1925; 2 boxes
    (pamphlets, books, folded maps in cloth- or leather-covered cases)
    - 1863. Travel and Personal Diary of Master James Bailey, calling card, 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Travel and personal Diary, expense account of J.A. Bailey while agent for Lake's Circus, photo of unidentified girl, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - 1876-1877. J.A. Bailey's personal memo book, receipts of main show 22 days each Sydney, seven days at Melbourne, list of employees and cages, 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Route book of Cooper, Bailey and Co., Great London Circus, Sanger's British Menagerie, International Allied Shows, 1879; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Route book of Cooper, Bailey and Co., Great London Circus and allied shows, 1880; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - 1896. Official "Souvenir" Buffalo Bill's Wild West and Congress of Rough Riders of the World. Ed. Bailey, Hutchinson, 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - 1898. Map and official route book, Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - 1899 Map and official route book, Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - 1902. Map, route book, and roster, Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - 1902-1904. Map and route book for tour of France, Italy, Austria, Hungary, Germany, and Belgium, Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - 1905. Map and route book for tour of France, Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - 1906. Map and route book for tour of France, Italy, Austria, Hungary, Germany, and Belgium, Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, 2 folders (Box 46, Folder 12-13)
    - 1895-1897. Routes, Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - 1891 through 1894. Route books for Adam Forepaugh Shows, 5 folders (Box 46, Folder 15-19)
    - P.T. Barnum 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884, 1885, & 1886 Route Books, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Robert Hunting 1894 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Barnum and Bailey, 1888-1906; 1 box
      - 1888, 1889, & 1890 Route Books, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - 1891 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - 1891 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - 1893, 1894, & 1895 Route Books, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - 1896 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - 1897 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - 1897-1898 Route Books, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - "Four Years in Europe," 1897-1901 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - 1903 Route Books, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - 1903-1904 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - 1903-1904 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - 1905 Route Books, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - 1906 Route Books, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Ringling Bros, 1882-1925; 1 box
      - Route of Ringling Bros. Shows, 1882-1900; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - 1882-1914 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Route of Ringling Bros. Shows, 1882-1925; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - 1892 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - 1892 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - 1897 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - 1897 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - 1901 Route Book, 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Illustrated Booklets, Couriers, 1871-1894; 2 boxes
    Folders #1-4, single items
    - Great International Circus, Handbook, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Hemmings and Cooper's Grand Consolidated Menagerie and Circus, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - John O'Brien's Great Six Tent $200,000 Challenge Show, 1873; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - VanAmburgh and Co.'s Illustrated Animalinac, 1871; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Copy of "Cooper and Bailey's International Programme", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Productions by "Order of Cincinnatus", 1888-1890; 1 box
      - Rome under Nero (three copies), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - 1888. Rhodopis, 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - 1889. Montezuma, or The Conquest of Mexico (two copies), 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - 1890. Moses, or The Bondage in Egypt, 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Productions by Imre and/or Bolossy Kiralfy, dates not examined; 1 box
      See Box 50, folder 6
      - Gorgeous Durbar at Delhi, by Bolossy Kiralfy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
        [missing 7/04]
      - Nero, or The Destruction of Rome, by Imre Kiralfy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Different copy of above, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Different copy of above, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Venice in London, by Imre Kiralfy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Fall of Babylon, by Imre Kiralfy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Venice, the Bride of the Sea, by Imre Kiralfy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - The Orient, by Bolossy Kiralfy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Forepaugh Shows, 1891-1894; 2 boxes
      - Forepaugh's Puzzle Book, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - "1776"-The American Revolution, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Adam Forepaugh Shows, 1891, Books of Wonders, 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Adam Forepaugh Shows, 1894, "In the Lead", 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Historic Scenes and Battles of the American Revolution, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - The American Revolution and the Scenes and Battles of "1776", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Fall of Nineveh, plot sheet, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Fall of Nineveh Courier, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Scenes and Battles of the American Revolution, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Beasts and Birds, Forepaugh's Menagerie, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Adam Forepaugh Shows, Musical Album, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - "Too White for Barnum", Forepaugh's reply to Barnum re. Forepaugh's Sacred White Elephant (copy also enclosed), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Adam Forepaugh Shows, 1891, Programme, 1 box (Box 49)
  - Illustrated Booklets (Barnum & Bailey, etc.), 1897-1934; 1 box
    - Two photos of main poles for canvas on cart pulled by eight in hand, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Buffalo Bill, 1897-1898; 1 box
      - Wild West, historical sketch and programme, 1897; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Wild West, historical sketch and programme, 1898 (Greater N.Y.), 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Bertram Mill's Circus, dates not examined; 1 box
      - at Olympia, 34-35, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - at Olympia, 35-36, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Newspaper clippings on the circus, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Pawnee Bill, 1934; 1 box
      - Ark-La-Tex Rodeo, Louisiana, 1934; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - P.T. Barnum, dates not examined; 1 box
      - i. Illustrated Catalogue and Guide Book to Barnum's American Museum (Readers to use Xerox only), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - ii. Sketch of Life, etc., of General Tom Thumb, (Charles S. Stratton) and his wife Laumia Warren Stratton, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - iii. Life of the living Aztec children, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - iv. History of animals and leading curiosities contained in P.T. Barnum's World Fair and Colosseum of Natural History and Art, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Barnum and Bailey, 1897-1900; 1 box
      - i. List of 12 staged productions in collex, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - ii. Coney Island, a spectacular water carnival, Olympia, 1898; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - iii. The Mahdi or For the Victoria Cross, Olympia, 1897-1898; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 6)